Which is why...
I've decided to sell you
to our neighbors in Parnacorta!
I really have been thrown out.
Saint Philia has arrived!
Welcome...
to Parnacorta.
I see now.
They paid a lot of money for me.
Of course they're handling me with care.
I'm sure my church duties will commence
the moment we arrive in the capital.
This might be my last chance to rest.
Capital City of Almburg, Parnacorta Kingdom
Saint Philia's
Welcome Party Venue
Welcome! So, so, so happy to have you,
Saint Philia!
Thank you for coming all this way!
I am Bjorn, the head of the church here.
We are truly, truly happy to have you!
You have our deepest gratitude
for joining us.
We welcome you with all our hearts!
Welcome!
Er... what are my duties today?
Needless to say, your duty...
to enjoy your welcome party!
Please, do help yourself!
Have some of these too, Saint Philia!
Ah... Thank you.
The Too-Perfect Saint: Tossed Aside
by My Fiancé and Sold to Another Kingdom
Episode 2
"Welcome to Parnacorta"
I always end up a
wallflower at these things.
It's good.
Hey!
How do you like the salad?
Delicious, right?
This man...
He was leading my escort.
I grew all those veggies myself.
It was a real struggle with what
little rainfall we've had this year.
He's a farmer?
If you'd like—
Prince Osvalt!
Prince?
There you are, Your Highness.
Prince Reichardt has been looking for...
Could it be that you haven't told her?
Yeah.
Saint Philia, forgive me for
failing to introduce you earlier.
This is the second prince of
our kingdom, Prince Osvalt.
The Kingdom of Parnacorta's Second Prince
Osvalt Parnacorta
It's a pleasure, Saint Philia.
This man is the second prince?!
I'll call Prince Reichardt over.
There's actually something
I wanted to tell you personally.
The truth is...
I'm sorry!
To buy a saint in such a fashion...
I'm sure it was an affront to your dignity.
We of this nation lost our previous saint.
When Girtonia reached out to us,
I took it as a godsend.
I'm sure you had to leave behind
family and loved ones in your homeland...
I've sworn an oath that I would
see to your every need,
though it won't make up for what you've lost.
I know how self-serving this is to say,
but I'll work hard to see that
you come to love our country.
I want to match your courage in coming here!
Me, coming to love this country?
That's what Prince Osvalt wants?
Love...
What? What does it mean to love again?
F-Forgive me. That was a little
overbearing, wasn't it?
N-Not at all.
Anyway, you were about to say
something about the veggies?
Ah, yes.
I can easily increase the rainfall
if you give me a few days.
I'm overstepping again.
You can?! That would be fantastic!
Oh? Sounds lively over here.
Would you mind introducing me as well?
This is the crown prince
of Parnacorta, Reichardt.
He's my big brother!
It's an honor to meet such
an extraordinary figure.
The Kingdom of Parnacorta's First Prince
Reichardt Parnacorta
I trust our kingdom will be in good hands.
O-Of course.
I'm sure I'm in good hands as well.
Two princes came
to meet me personally...
That shows just how much they're
expecting of me. It's a lot of pressure.
And so Philia, the girl sold by her homeland,
begins her life as Parnacorta's saint.
Hold on. Have your prices gone up again?
Sorry. Monsters are appearing
on the roads again.
I'm having a hard time getting stock in, too.
This never happened when
the saint was around...
It's still hard to believe
Saint Elizabeth is dead.
Yeah. We'll never know
anyone so kind ever again.
Speaking of, I hear there's
a new saint in the kingdom.
Yeah, I saw her!
She just arrived, didn't she?
Still...
I know. She seems rather
unapproachable, doesn't she?
This place is...
This will be your new home.
It's twice as big as our family home.
That's right.
I arrived in Parnacorta yesterday.
I want you to come to love this country.
To love this country...
I have to work harder than ever before.
Saint Philia?
What are you doing up and about this early?
You can rest a bit longer if you'd like.
Butler
Leonardo
Maid
Lena
What? But my saintly duties...
I'm sorry, but would you mind
preparing something for me?
The Kingdom of Parnacorta...
Located at the center of the continent,
it is bordered by five other countries.
The nation is lush with greenery and
surrounded by mountains and forests.
Its capital city of Almburg
lies at the heart of it all.
But the mountainous woods are perfect
nesting grounds for monsters,
which makes Parnacorta a frequent target.
Parnacorta sits in a basin.
It's mountains and forests all around.
My first destination should be...
What are you seeing in that map?
Is something the matter?
No...
Although, er... could I
ask why you're both here?
We have been assigned
to see to your every need.
Which means supporting
you in your duties, too!
You sure surprised me, though.
You're an early riser!
On your first day, at that!
You must be raring to go.
Er... this is more or less
my routine every day.
Every day?!
Yes. To fully fulfill my duties as saint,
I must start early or I won't finish in time.
So that's how things were in Girtonia?
What are you trying
to find on that map, then?
Ah, right.
I'm using it to identify potential
monster nesting grounds.
You can guess, to a degree, by the terrain.
Then our destination is...
Yes. We'll start...
with the Detrauhorn Mountains to the north.
The Too-Perfect Saint: Tossed Aside
by My Fiancé and Sold to Another Kingdom
A sky black with clouds.
An atmosphere so oppressive
it's hard to breathe.
The presence of many monsters.
I think...
waiting any longer to deal with this
could have led to disaster.
The monster nest here
is larger than I anticipated.
It may be dangerous. Please stand back.
No...
We have been entrusted with
your safety, Saint Philia!
By all means, focus on
establishing your barrier.
Uh... okay.
I'm sure they're just watching me
to make sure I do my job properly.
But this my first time working
with anyone else around,
so it's a little distracting.
By the way, Mr. Leonardo...
You were on Saint Elizabeth's
security detail too, weren't you?
Yes, and I protected her predecessor as well.
I never got to see the last saint in action!
How exactly do they erect
one of those barrier things?
This should be a good spot.
Let's begin.
The saint prays to the divine,
conjuring several pillars
of light to support the barrier.
The barrier forms over the land
enclosed by the pillars.
That area becomes a holy sanctuary
in which monsters are weakened.
Holy Sanctuary
The more pillars she erects,
the more powerful the barrier.
Holy Sanctuary
But ordinarily, it is said
to take many hours,
up to a dozen or more,
to erect but one pillar.
As it consumes copious mental,
physical, and magical energy,
it is an impressive feat to conjure
even a single pillar in a day.
That is why Saint Philia
needs people to protect her.
I see!
I've completed the first pillar.
But it's only been thirty minutes!
Yes. I need to make seven more.
Taking travel time into account,
it may take us past lunch.
I thought it was a big deal
to make just one a day?
It is.
A pillar of light in just thirty minutes?
I've never heard of such a thing. This is...
Prince Osvalt, you've brought
someone extraordinary into our midst.
Wow! The atmosphere is totally different!
Well done creating the barrier.
Now, we should return to the mansion—
No.
We'll stay and research the
local ecosystem and vegetation.
The information could prove useful later.
Then we'll erect a barrier in the
mountains to the west as well.
S-Saint Philia!
Wait for us!
I'm sorry I kept you out so late.
Not at all! It was an impressive first day.
But seriously...
What a shock...
Saint Philia never gave us a break!
I would have liked to create
a few more barriers,
then begin preparing the rain
ritual Prince Osvalt asked for...
SHUDDER
I wasn't expecting you to beg me to stop.
Saint Philia! How can you want to do more?
You're already overworked!
If you collapse from exhaustion,
it'll be on our heads!
You've already done three times the work
of the most storied saints in history.
We stopped by towns to speak with locals,
you thought up medicinal
recipes in the carriage,
and even drew up plans for a dam...
That was really something else.
But that other stuff isn't really
part of a saint's job, is it?
Is it not?
Not from what I've heard, at least...
A saint exists to rid the land
of all the plagues it.
Medicine, pharmaceutics,
agriculture, engineering...
I was taught to be ready
to deal with anything.
That reminds me. When I kept developing
new medicines, Prince Julius said...
The herbalist made nasty comments about you
and filed a complaint
by the medical board to us.
Can't you just stay out of things?
This is why I say you lack charm.
Regardless, let us take some
time off tomorrow.
Your health may suffer if
you continue at this rate.
Time off, you say?
Why is she acting like she's
never of it before?!
Leonardo's Special Spiced Hot Milk
But won't your saint taking time
off harm national interests?
No! Your health is more important
than national interests!
Don't push yourself so hard!
You only just got here as it is!
They're saying the opposite
of what my mother did...
But the kingdom is in a perilous state.
At least let me erect barriers
in the east and south tomorrow.
As saint, I cannot compromise on that.
You watched her all day today.
What did you think?
Saint Philia, you mean?
She seems so earnest and determined,
but she's also a bit awkward and helpless.
And charming to boot!
I think I might really like her a lot.
But something's strange about her.
It seems like she'd rather work on her own.
Prince Osvalt said that when
she reached our territory,
she hadn't a single escort with her,
let alone an attendant.
But that seems so wrong, doesn't it?
I mean, she's a saint.
A saint is like a country's leader...
She should be a noble!
How in the world was Girtonia treating her?
I want Saint Philia to take
better care of herself!
Yes.
So I'm going to see to her every
need and really pamper her!
I want to show her soon
just how much she means to us!
Have you heard about everything
the new saint's done?
Yeah, we got new stock in
for the first time in ages!
From what I heard, she worked herself
to the bone for us from dawn until dusk!
To think we'd follow up Saint Elizabeth
with another wonderful saint...
We're all so lucky!
My sister, Philia, was always perfect.
The strength her saintly powers,
her wealth of knowledge far beyond her years,
her kindness and sincerity...
I truly admired her.
I always thought that as long as I
followed her example, I'd be okay!
But...
now...
Silver Judgment!
Without her as a role model...
what am I to do?
E-Emergency, Your Highness!
Highness!
Monsters have begun surging
all over the kingdom!
The hunts can't keep up!
Why now?
Haven't I been sending out
regular hunting parties?
W-Well, actually...
This says no one actually deployed.
Saint Philia always said
she'd take care of it, so...
Those morons!
After I finally got her out of my hair...
We have money now! Do whatever it
takes to vanquish the monsters!
Don't let them reach the capital!
Attention!
Things are a lot noisier around
here with Saint Philia gone.
March!
Sir!
The traveling merchant I always
buy from hasn't been by.
No need to worry.
Saint Mia will see to everything!
It's strange.
It's all too strange.
Not this situation, but what
led up to it in the first place.
I mean...
my sister left for a neighboring
kingdom without saying a word to me?
Father!
Why has my sister gone to Parnacorta?
If they needed a saint, they should have
asked for me! I wasn't even engaged yet!
Mia.
Don't make me say it again.
It was Philia's decision to leave.
My sister was the perfect saint.
She would never leave without talking to me
or arranging a handoff of duties.
The fact that she didn't...
Either it was all just that sudden...
or she wasn't allowed to.
Who would do something so awful?
Whoever took my sister from me...
I'll take them to task.
The Too-Perfect Saint: Tossed Aside
by My Fiancé and Sold to Another Kingdom.
Next time, episode 3:
Next Time
Episode 3
"Our First  Date"
"Our First Date."